Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design,Corcoran Gallery of Art education department records 1961-2010 COR0006.0.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Exhibitions [2016 processing project], 1960-2006; Series 18
  - Object Lessons - Fred Wilson, Undated; Series 18 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Baltimore Museum of Art 93, 1993; Series 18 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - CGA Works byAfrican-American Artists, Undated; Series 18 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - African American Artists - Accession Records, Labels, Artist info., Undated; Series 18 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Gift Checklist: The Gordon Parks Collection, Undated; Series 18 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Family Medicine: The Art of Elizabeth Talford Scott Brochure, Undated; Series 18 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Evans-Tibbs Collection, Undated; Series 18 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - CGA Zip Disks, Undated; Series 18 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Nat'l Endowment for the Arts Final Descriptive Report FY 1998, 1998-1999; Series 18 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - A-A Artists: School Package, Undated; Series 18 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - A-A Art at Corcoran Notes and Correspondences, Undated; Series 18 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - A-A at Corcoran Final Organization, 1999 July 1; Series 18 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - CGA Master art slides, Undated; Series 18 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - A-A School Tour Pkg. Slides / Repros., Undated; Series 18 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - A-A School Pkg. 2-Design / Designers, Undated; Series 18 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - A-A School Pkg. Analysis & Activs., Undated; Series 18 (Box 56, Folder 21)
- Grants [2016 processing project], 1987-1997; Series 19
  - D.C. Commis. of Arts Financial Report, Circa 1987-1997; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Lila Wallace - Reader's Digest Fund Application Form, Circa 1987-1997; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Lila Wallace Grant Proposal, 1993-1994; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Starr Foundation, 1990; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Report of NEH Grants Given '89, 1989; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Junior League Grant, 1991; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1989-1990; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Grants (Times-Journal), Circa 1987-1997; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - NEA - Long Range Special Artistic Initiative '89, 1989; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Conservation Grant, Circa 1987-1997; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Andy Warhol Foundation, Circa 1987-1997; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Andy Warhol Foundation Approved Grant, Circa 1987-1997; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - 1988 Rep. on Arts Ed. from NEA, Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - IBM 1990, Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - IMS Grrant Application - 1990, Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Fundraising Seminnar June '90, 1990 June; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Reading is Fundamental 1988-1989, Circa 1987-1997; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - DC Commission Grant '89, 1989; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Graham Meyer, Strong Foundats. Comp. "Artrisk", Circa 1987-1997; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - NEA: Computer Tours 1991-93, 1991-1993; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Washington Post / School Program, Circa 1987-1997; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Journal Newspapers Support, Circa 1987-1997; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Garnett Foundation, Circa 1987-1997; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Getty Project: Focus Group I '89, 1989; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Campbell Soup Foundation Proposal, Circa 1987-1997; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Gannett Foundation 1989-90, 1989-1990; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Poss. Historians for an NEH Grant w/ Consult's on Coll/CGA '87, 1987; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - NEH 1979 Grants, 1987; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Grant Proposal to DC Commi'sn 1979 for Discov. Amer. Units, Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - NEH 1993, Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Hearst Found. Operating Support Grant 1982, Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Cafritz Foundation Application 3/92, 1992 March; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - nathan Cummings Foundation June, 1990, 1990 June; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Educational Funding Target Goals, 1990-1991; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Institutional Vision (Dvlpmt), 1988-1992; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - ARCO Foundation 90-91, 1990-1991; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Hearst Foundation Proposal, 1989 December 18; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - General Support, Circa 1987-1997; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - 88 Development / Project Support Text for Gen. Developm. Opportunities Piece, 1988; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Storyteller's Circle & Sunday Traditions (NEA), 1993; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Grants 1990-97, 1990-1997; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Corporate Participation, Circa 1987-1997; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - D.C. Commission Family Day Grant, 1994-1997; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - D.C. Commis'n Grant: 90-91, 1990-1991; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - NEA - Education & Access Grant, 1997 April 7; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Loose Documents, 1996-1997; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - Grant Stuff 1997, Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - Grants-pastt, Circa 1987-1997; Series 19 (Box 26, Folder 48)
- Programs files [2016 processing project], 2003-2013; Series 20
  - Comix 101, 2009; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - The Installation of Systematic Landscapes Panel, 2009 May 21; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Gilbert Rhode: Modern Design Phyllis Ross, 2009 May 7; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - MAS: Klavier Trio Amsterdam, 2009 May 3; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Presidential Plantations Tour, 2009 April 24; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Refining Urbanism William Morris, 2009 April 28; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Nature Informs Interior Design Stephen Drucker, 2009 April 23; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Terminal Mirage, Lake Project, and Mining Project David Maisel, 2009 April 15; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Ralph Rucci: A Designer and His House David Boatman, 2009 April 7; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - CMF Verge Ensemble, 2009 April 5; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - The Gardner Heist Ulrich Baser, 2009 April 2; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Dariing Joyful Landscapes Wolfgang Oehme, 2009 March 30; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Healy Portrait Curator's Talk Sarah Cash, 2009 March 26; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Naturally Fashionable Summer Rayne Oaks, 2009 March 25; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - MAS: Ariel Quartet and Roger Tapping, 2009 March 22; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Invisible Abbott Thayer, 2009 March 17; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - A Strong Clear Vision Maya Lin, 2009 March 16; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Maya Lin, 2009 March 11; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Seven Days in the Art World Sarah Throton, 2009 March; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Ilya and Emilia Kabakov in Dialogue, 2009 February 24; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - The Designing Type Mathew Carter, 2009 February; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Alexis Bittar, 2009 February 11; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Timeless Existance Rajesh Nair, 2009 February 10; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - MAS: Auryn Quartet, 2009 February 8; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Dwelling on Design Sam Grave, 2009 February 2; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Old Masters, New Worl: Cynthia Saltzman, 2009 January 29; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - MAS: Triple Helix Piano Trio, 2009 January 25; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Chicago Consipracy Trial Weinglass and Hayden, 2009 January 22; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 28)
  - Chervolution Trisha Ziff, 2009 January 21; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 29)
  - Science as Art Jonah Lehrer, 2009 January 12; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 30)
  - Sparkling in the City Trip to NYC, 2008 December 12; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 31)
  - Fashion Portrays Power Robin Givhan, 2008 December 11; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 32)
  - Performing Avedon Adam Gopnik, 2008 December 10; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 33)
  - At Work Annie Leibovitz, 2008 December 8; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 34)
  - Avedon: Fashion Photographs, 1945-2000 Carol Squiers, 2008 December 2; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 35)
  - From Inspiration to Runway Daniel Vosovic, 2008 December 1; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 36)
  - David Yurman, 2008 November 18; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 37)
  - In Spite of Myself Christopher Plummer, 2008 November 17; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 38)
  - Gallery Talk on The Family Will Stapp, 2008 November 13; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 39)
  - Darkenss and Light Richard Avedon, 2008 November 11; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 40)
  - MAS: Takacs Quartet, 2008 November 9; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 41)
  - Wounded Cities Leo Rubinfien, 2008 November 5; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 42)
  - Insider Trends for Fall '08 and Spring '09 Edward Allen, 2008 October 30; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 43)
  - MAS: Peabody Trio, 2008 October 26; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 44)
  - Power Play Arachne Aerial Arts, 2008 October 20; Series 20 (Box 61, Folder 45)
  - Architecture as Continuum Charles Gwathmey, 2008 April 8; Series 20 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Designing Green Graig Dykers, 2008 April 3; Series 20 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Jupiter String Quartet, 2008 March 28; Series 20 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Perspective Talk: The Corcoran Collects Marisa Bourgoin, 2008 March 27; Series 20 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Best Cellar's Presents an American Tour of Wine Brett Freeman, Circa 2004-2008; Series 20 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Waste = Food: Environmental Movements in Design Lance Hosey, 2008 March 13; Series 20 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Dead Men's Hollow, 2008 March 6; Series 20 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - At Home with History, 2008 March 5; Series 20 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - David Berman, 2008 February 28; Series 20 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - MES: Takacs Quartet, 2008 February 22; Series 20 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Future by Design William Gozecki, 2008 February 20; Series 20 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Lithuania National Day Celebration Vytautas Landsbergis, 2008 February 11; Series 20 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Art Basel Miami Tour, 2006; Series 20 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Art Basel Miami, 2004; Series 20 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - MES 2006-2007 Season, Series 20 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - MES 2007-2008 Series, Series 20 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - [Art and the Human Experience A Community Connection], Circa 2004-2008; Series 20 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - MAS: Klavier Trio Amsterdam, 2010 March 29; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - The Woodmans Screening A Scott Willis Film, 2010 March 24; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Eadweard Muybridge: 200 Photographer, 2010 March 23; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Impressionism and Politics Lecture Richard Brettel, 2010 March 11; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Nancy Locke on Paul Cezanne, 2010 March 8; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Thomas Deman Funded Lecture, 2010 March 2; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Milton Glasser: To Inform & Delight, 2010 March 10; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Camille Pisarro & Vincent van Gogh, 2010 February 24; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Michael Taylor: James Dean of Interior Design, 2010 February 22; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Dressed to Dance, 2010 February 8; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Morgan Spurlock, 2010 February 2; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Triple Helix Piano Trio, 2010 January 31; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Turner to Cezanne: An Evening With Beatrice Golton Corcoran Scholars Paul Greenhalgh, 2010 January 29; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Lecture Oliver Fairclough, 2010 January 27; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Lecture & Presentation David Doubilet, 2010 January 13; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Stefan Sangeister: Design & Happiness, 2010 January 11; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Verge Ensemble, 2010 January 10; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Barbara Prey Gallery Talk, 2009 December 17; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - James Rosenquist: Painting Below Zero, 2009 December 15; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - FIOM 2009 Debut Nick Verreos, 2009 December 9; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Glimmer Warren Berger, 2009 November 17; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Edward Burtynsky, 2009 November 11; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Washington Perels: Songs of the Sea & Shore, 2009 November 10; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Woman as Design Stephen Bayley, 2009 November 9; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Sargent & The Sea: A Symposium, 2009 November 7; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Kirk Pillow on the Sublime, 2009 November 3; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Painting Madame X, 2009 October 14; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - An Evening with Michael Smith, 2009 October 27; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Now Enseble Judd Greenstein, 2009 October 19; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - The Bauhaus Group Nicholas Fox Weber, 2009 October 16; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Sargent & The Sea Sarah Cash, 2009 October 8; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - MAS: Jupiter String Quartet, 2009 October 4; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - Edward Burtynsky: Oil William Rees, 2009 October 3; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Kentuck Knob & Falling Water Bus Tour, 2009 October 2; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 34)
  - Fierce Style Christian Siriano, 2009 November 3; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 35)
  - Culture Clash: Meatloaf, Mayonnasie, & Bidets Nicole Cotroneo, 2009 September 29; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 36)
  - Died Young, Stayed Pretty Eileen Yaghoobian, 2009 September 24; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 37)
  - Leon Krick Talk, 2009 September 23; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 38)
  - Herb & Dorothy Megumi Sasaki, 2009 September 15; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 39)
  - Verge Ensemble, 2009 September 13; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 40)
  - Jim Reed Lecture, 2009 July 29; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 41)
  - Design & Details: Materials & Their Effects Cooper Hewitt National Design Awards, 2009 July 24; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 42)
  - In the Valley of the Kings Daniel Meyerson, 2009 July 20; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 43)
  - Jamie Drake, 2009 July 14; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 44)
  - Creating Characters: An Illustrative Evening Mary Grandpre, 2009 July 13; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 45)
  - William Eggleston in the Real World Screening, 2009 July 9; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 46)
  - Objectified Screening Gary Hustwit, 2009 July; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 47)
  - Special Preview Debate Tooby, Thomas & Gower, 2009 June 26; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 48)
  - Knossos and the Prophets of Modernism Cathy Gere, 2009 June 25; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 49)
  - Eggleston & Almereyda, 2009 June 17; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 50)
  - MAS: Jupiter Quartet, 2009 May 31; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 51)
  - Fame and Frame Pat Verde, 2009 May 26; Series 20 (Box 63, Folder 52)
  - Roger Gastman, 2011 March 17; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - The Artful Garden Sheila Brady, 2011 March 1; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Trio Quelque Chose, 2011 February 28; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Paul Richard: Color Paintings Pedigree, 2011 February 24; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Give Me Your Hand Dermot Crowley & Dearbhla Molloy, 2011 February 13; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - MAS: Klavier Trio Amsterdam, 2011 February 4; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - The Cool School, 2011 February 3; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - MES: Ariel Quartet & Roger Tapping, 2011 January 25; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Preserving the Washington Color School Paintings Jay Krueger, 2011 January 20; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Art Jamz January 2011, 2011 January; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Spencer Finch Lecture and Q&A, 2010 December 14; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - The Nature of Art: The Work of John Alexander, 2010 December 9; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - The Aesthetic of the Dream in Surrealist Film: Bernard Welt, 2010 December 8; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Dana Taisoon Burgess and Company, 2010 December; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Knoll: A Modernist Universe Book Signing and Reception, 2010 December 2; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Betan Court and Sherrill Lecture, Book Signing and Sale, 2010 November 29; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Corine May Botz: Lecture and Book Signing/Sale, 2010 November 22; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Furia Flamenca: Pasion Gitana, 2010 November 17; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Ippalita, 2010 November 15; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Photography at the Corcoran Talk Amanda Maddox, 2010 November 13; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - ADOBE Julianne Kost, 2010 November 13; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Tim Hetherington: Infidel, 2010 November 11; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Annual Newman Lecture Burce Davidson, 2010 November 6; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - rick Valicenti's Thirst, 2010 November 3; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Marian Bantjes Lecture and Q&A, 2010 October 28; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Kevin Barker's Screening of "The Family Jams", 2010 October 26; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Chris Madden: The Soul of a House, 2010 October 20; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 27)
  - Rebecca Moses, 2010 October 12; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 28)
  - Brian STorm, 2010 October 1; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 29)
  - Musical Evening Series: Danish String Quartet, 2010 October 8; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 30)
  - Seymour Chwast, 2010 September 22; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 31)
  - Presiden'ts Photogrophers, 2010 September 20; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 32)
  - Puttin on the Ritz: Steve Ross, 2010 September 20; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 33)
  - Verge Ensemble, 2010 September 19; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 34)
  - An Evening with Philip Glass, 2010 September 9; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 35)
  - Washington Revels, 2010 September 4; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 36)
  - I Love Design; NYC Bus Tour, 2010 July 30; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 37)
  - Chuck Close Film Screening, 2010 July 21; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 38)
  - Montage Music Society: Starry Night Project, 2010 July 17; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 39)
  - Bernard - Cinema, 2010 July 14; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 40)
  - Steve Salny on Frances Elkins, 2010 July 13; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 41)
  - Chuck Close & Chris Finch, 2010 June 30; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 42)
  - WOCO Garden Tour, 2010 June 11; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 43)
  - Art Jamz June 2010, 2010 June 1; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 44)
  - FSS: Verge, 2010 June 12; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 45)
  - Play it Forward Kinetic Art Tim Fort, 2010 July 10; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 46)
  - Art of the Steal, 2010 June 8; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 47)
  - Thomas Obrien: American Modern, 2010 May 17; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 48)
  - All Senior Gallery Talk, 2010 May 13; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 49)
  - Estonian Pianist Minkel Poll, 2010 May 10; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 50)
  - Back to the Future: Arggentina Copello Dudley Memorial Lecture, 2010 May 8; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 51)
  - Guilded Age Guerilla: Edith Wharton & Her Design Revolution, 2010 May 5; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 52)
  - Ariel & Roger Quartet Tapping, 2010 May 2; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 53)
  - Verge Ensemble, 2010 April 25; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 54)
  - Bus Tour to the Barnest BMA, 2010 April 23; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 55)
  - Gillian Forrester, 2010 April 22; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 56)
  - FGI Eco-Chic, 2010 April 21; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 57)
  - Philipoh Muybridge, 2010 April 20; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 58)
  - C Hall Memorial Concert, 2010 April 19; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 59)
  - The Places in Between Arachne Aerial Arts, 2010 April 13; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 60)
  - Muybridge & the Evolution of Landscapes Mark Klott, 2010 April 7; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 61)
  - Socrates Sculpture Park/WPA, 2010 April 6; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 62)
  - Die Schone Mullerin, 2010 March 24; Series 20 (Box 64, Folder 63)
  - CGA People to People Travel Proram Packet 2011, 2011 November 12-19; Series 20 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Cuba Evaluations, 2012; Series 20 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Participants CGA 2005, Series 20 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Bus / Rests / Flights 2005, Series 20 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Gen. Finances 2005, Series 20 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Hotel Oct. 4th 2005, 2005 October 4; Series 20 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Santa Fe 2006, Series 20 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Miami 2003, Series 20 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Japan 2005-2006, Series 20 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Participants Japan 2006, Series 20 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Cuba 4 - Apps and $ 2003, Series 20 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Tuscany 2002, Series 20 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Tuba 2001, Series 20 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Art Based Miami Beach Dec, 2003, 2003 December; Series 20 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Cuba 2002-2003, Series 20 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Cuba 2005, Series 20 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - 5 Cuba - app forms, $ 2003, Series 20 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - American Impressionism Art Trail 2005, Series 20 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Extra Itineraries to pass out 2005, Series 20 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - CT Trip 2007, Series 20 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Hudson River Valley October 2008, 2008 October; Series 20 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Culture Trip - Participants, Corresp., Finances 2004, Series 20 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Joan Mitchell Film, 2011 March 10; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - EFF Vincent Scully, 2011 March 21; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Hugo Wolf, 2011 March 25; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Ben Katchor, 2011 March 29; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Sarah Cash, 2011 March 31; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Culture Wars: Then Now, 2011 March 26; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Ellen Miles, 2011 April 14; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Verge, 2011 April 17; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Jenny Carson, 2011 April 21; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Emily Shapiro, 2011 May 5; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Bill Cunningham: New York, 2011 July 8; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Next Gallery Talks, 2011; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Next Panel, 2011 May 12; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Art/Poetry, 2011 May 13; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Kerry Roeder AP Cat Gallery, 2011 May 19; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Mona Hajj, 2011 April 20; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - John Robshaw, 2011 May 25; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Chajana den Harder, 2011 May 28; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - APCAT Lee Glazer, 2011 June 2; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Verna Curtis, 2011 June 23; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - Azar Nafisi, 2011 July 13; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - Adam Greenhalgh AP CAT Gallery Talk, 2011 July 21; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Art Jamz, 2011 August 1; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - Chris Martin, 2011 September 8; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 24)
  - Grace Before Dying, 2011 September 9; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 25)
  - Verge, 2011 September 18; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 26)
  - Dowtown Scene Films, 2011; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 27)
  - Rubells Talk, 2011 September 26; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 28)
  - Dudley, 2011 October 3; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Nina Chanel Abney, 2011 October 6; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 30)
  - Kalup Linzt Hasan, 2011 October 20; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 31)
  - Kentuck Knob Falling Water, 2011 October 14; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 32)
  - Glenn Ligon, 2011 November 1; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 33)
  - Richard Thompson, 2011 November 1; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 34)
  - Panel - WPA Shinique Smith, 2011 November 3; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 35)
  - Newman Lecture: Carrie Mae Weems, 2011 November 12; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 36)
  - Paul Greenhalgh: Fair World, 2011 November 16; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 37)
  - Under the Influence Artist Evening with John Bankston, 2011 November 17; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 38)
  - Hank Willis Thomas, 2011 November 28; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 39)